https://sigatransformers.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Home
About Us
Why Us?
Email: info@sigatransformers.co.uk
Web:
www.sigatransformers.co.uk
Privacy Policy
Who we are
In this privacy policy references to “we”, “us” and “our” are to SIGA (Electronics) Ltd. References to “our Website” or “the Website” are to www.sigatransformers.co.uk.
What information we collect and how
The information we collect via the Website may include.
1. Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.
2. Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).
3. Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website.
What we do with your information
Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used:
1. To process your order, to provide after sales service (we may pass your details to another organisation to supply/deliver products or services you have purchased and/or to provide after-sales service);
2. In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information on our other products and services. In such a case you will be offered the option to opt in/out before completing your purchase.
We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.
Your Rights
You have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address, telephone number and email.
Privacy
SIGA (Electronics) Ltd
3 Darlington Close
Sunderland Road
Sandy
Beds
SG19 1RW
Other Websites
This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.
The company has a simple objective to provide an efficient service
to the customer ensuring that...
Components are supplied conforming to the required specification
Components are supplied to the required quality.
Components are supplied on time.
TestimonialsThank you for all your efforts in turning these around quickly HM, Purchasing Manager,Engine manufacturer
Business Address and Registered office:
SIGA (Electronics) Ltd, 3 Darlington Close, Sunderland Road, Sandy, Bedfordshire, England, SG19 1RW
Home
About Us
Why Us?
